const srpPitanjaLvl3 = [
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "М И Л К А И Ц А",
        correctAnswer: "камилица",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "В А Н Д А Л А",
        correctAnswer: "лаванда",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "Н А М Е Т",
        correctAnswer: "мента",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "М А Н И Л А",
        correctAnswer: "малина",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "З Е Б Р А",
        correctAnswer: "бреза",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "С Т Р А Х",
        correctAnswer: "храст",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "Г А Б Р Е М",
        correctAnswer: "багрем",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "Б У В А К",
        correctAnswer: "буква",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "Г О Н И К",
        correctAnswer: "гинко",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "К О П Р А В И",
        correctAnswer: "коприва",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "Р О Б",
        correctAnswer: "бор",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "М О С К В А",
        correctAnswer: "смоква",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "П И Л А",
        correctAnswer: "липа",
    },
    {
        question: "Поставити слова на њихово исправно мјесто како би се добио исправан назив биљке",
        letters: "М И Л У Н",
        correctAnswer: "лимун",
    }
];

export default srpPitanjaLvl3